Guide to the Duplex Advertising Company. Billboard Images and Records, 1964-1993 and undated RL.00339
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Negatives Series, 1978-1985 and undated
  - Loose negatives (Duplex Advertising)
    - Hardees, undated, sleeve #55 (Box 11)
    - HBO/Cablevision, sleeve #46 (Box 11)
    - Heart O'Texas Fair and Rodeo, 1980 Nov. 14, sleeve # 44 (Box 11)
    - Heartfield Funeral Home, 1980 Aug. 7, sleeve # 43 (Box 11)
    - Hele Mai Restaurant, 1979 Mar. 23, sleeve # 51 (Box 11)
    - HGH, Inc., builder and developer, 1970s, sleeve # 49 (Box 11)
    - Hill Country Furniture, 1979 Mar. 23, sleeve # 51 (Box 11)
    - Hill Funeral Chapel, undated, sleeve # 19 (Box 11)
    - Hobie Cat Outdoor Adventurers, undated, sleeve #46 (Box 11)
    - Holiday Inn, undated, sleeve # 18 (Box 11)
    - Holland Corn Festival, 1980 June 20, sleeve # 45 (Box 11)
    - Hotels and motels, undated, sleeve #14, 31, 32 (Box 11)
    - Ice Capades, undated, sleeve # 20 (Box 11)
    - Interior design, undated, sleeve #23, 24, 28 (Box 11)
    - Jaycees, 1979 Mar. 23, sleeve # 51 (Box 11)
    - J.C. Penny, 1978 June 28, sleeve # 11 (Box 11)
    - Jewelers, undated, sleeve #14 (Box 11)
    - Jewelry
      - 1978 Dec. 13, sleeve # 13 (Box 11)
      - Undated, sleeves #16, 23 (Box 11)
    - Johnson's Office Machines, undated, sleeve #56, 57 (Box 11)
    - Kentucky Fried Chicken
      - 1970s, sleeve # 49 (Box 11)
      - 1978 June 28, sleeve # 11 (Box 11)
      - 1979 Mar. 26, sleeve # 50 (Box 11)
    - King's Fried Chicken
      - 1980 Aug. 22, sleeve # 48b (Box 11)
      - Undated, sleeves #19, 46 (Box 11)
    - KIXS FM
      - 1978 Sept. 21, sleeve # 10 (Box 11)
      - Undated, sleeves #17, 19 (Box 11)
    - KTEM 14, 1979 Mar. 26, sleeve # 50 (Box 11)
    - Lakeway Inn, undated, sleeve # 46 (Box 11)
    - Laughter Hours (NBC), undated, sleeve # 19 (Box 11)
    - Lewis Chiropractor, undated, sleeve # 52 (Box 11)
    - Lone Star Alcohol, undated, sleeve # 56 (Box 11)
    - Lone Star Beer, undated, sleeve # 52 (Box 11)
    - Longhorn Cavern State Park, undated, sleeve #46 (Box 11)
    - Marina, undated, sleeve #20 (Box 11)
    - Marboro Menthol cigarettes, undated, sleeve #53 (Box 11)
    - Merchant's Health Expo, undated, sleeve # 52 (Box 11)
    - Military, undated, sleeve #35 (Box 11)
    - Mobile home parks, undated, sleeve #33 (Box 11)
    - Mobile homes, undated, sleeve #15 (Box 11)
    - Music, undated, sleeve #35 (Box 11)
    - Mustang Drive-In, undated, sleeve # 18 (Box 11)
    - National Bank, 1980 Aug. 7, sleeve # 43 (Box 11)
    - Natural Bridge Caverns, undated, sleeve # 46 (Box 11)
    - NBC, undated, sleeve #57 (Box 11)
    - Non-advertising images
      - 1970s, sleeve # 49 (Box 11)
      - 1978 July 14, sleeve # 12 (Box 11)
      - 1979 Mar. 23, sleeve # 51 (Box 11)
      - 1980 June 20, sleeve # 45 (Box 11)
      - 1980 Aug. 7, sleeve # 43 (Box 11)
      - 1980 Nov. 14, sleeve # 44 (Box 11)
      - Undated, sleeves #35, 42, 54-56 (Box 11)
    - Oak Creek Homes, sleeve #52 (Box 11)
    - Oak Hills Custom Homes, undated, sleeve # 46 (Box 11)
    - Opa's Smoked Ham, undated, sleeve # 18 (Box 11)
    - Optical services, undated, sleeve #22, 23 (Box 11)
    - Outdoor advertising, undated, sleeve #21 (Box 11)
    - Palm Harbor Homes, undated, sleeve # 55 (Box 11)
    - Partner Dance Club
      - 1980 Aug. 22, sleeve # 48a (Box 11)
      - Undated, sleeve #20 (Box 11)
    - People's National Bank, undated, sleeve # 17 (Box 11)
    - Pesticides, undated, sleeve #26 (Box 11)
    - Pharmacies, undated, sleeve #26 (Box 11)
    - Piccadilly Cafeteria, 1979 Mar. 26, sleeve # 50 (Box 11)
    - Pizza, undated, sleeve #20 (Box 11)
    - Plumbing, undated, sleeves #24, 29 (Box 11)
    - Public safety, undated, sleeve #52 (Box 11)
    - Public service
      - 1980 Nov. 14, sleeve # 44 (Box 11)
      - Undated, sleeves #19, 21, 22, 25, 29-32, 34, 35, 52, 53, 55-57 (Box 11)
    - Radio
      - 1978 Dec. 13, sleeve # 25 (Box 11)
      - Undated, sleeves #13, 27, 29, 30, 32, 33, 34 (Box 11)
    - Raedeans Ladies Fashions, 1980 June 20, sleeve # 45 (Box 11)
    - Raid, 1980 Aug. 7, sleeve #43 (Box 11)
    - Ranch House Restaurant, undated, sleeve # 55 (Box 11)
    - Real estate, undated, sleeves #16, 21, 27-30, 32-35 (Box 11)
    - Restaurants
      - 1978 Dec. 13, sleeve # 13 (Box 11)
      - Undated, sleeves #14, 16, 21-23, 25-33, 40a-b (Box 11)
    - Retail, undated, sleeves #22-35, 41 (Box 11)
    - Richter Furniture
      - 1970s, sleeve # 49 (Box 11)
      - Undated, sleeves #18, 19 (Box 11)
    - River Place Restaurant, 1980 Aug. 7, sleeve # 43 (Box 11)
    - Rockdale State Bank, 1970s, sleeve # 49 (Box 11)
    - Round Rock Furniture, undated, sleeve # 17 (Box 11)
    - Russel's GMC, undated, sleeve # 52 (Box 11)
    - Sambo's Restaurant, undated, sleeve # 20 (Box 11)
    - Scenes from the highway
      - 1979 Sept. 17, sleeve # 47 (Box 11)
      - 1980 Aug. 22, sleeve # 48a (Box 11)
    - Schlotsky's, undated, sleeve # 17 (Box 11)
    - Security State Bank and Trust
      - 1980 Nov. 14, sleeve # 44 (Box 11)
      - Undated, sleeves #18, 19 (Box 11)
    - Sheffield Funeral Home, 1980 Aug. 22, sleeve # 48a (Box 11)
    - Shoes, undated, sleeve #23 (Box 11)
    - Silver Post Jewelry
      - 1979 Mar. 23, sleeve # 51 (Box 11)
      - 1979 Sept. 21, sleeve # 10 (Box 11)
      - 1980 Aug. 7, sleeve # 43 (Box 11)
    - Sound Emporium, 1979 Mar. 26, sleeve # 50 (Box 11)
    - Southport Homes, undated, sleeve # 46 (Box 11)
    - Specialty Shop, 1980 June 20, sleeve # 45 (Box 11)
    - Stagecoach Inn, undated, sleeve # 54 (Box 11)
    - Steger Gunberg R.V. Center, 1979 Mar. 26, sleeve # 50 (Box 11)
    - Television, undated, sleeve #15 (Box 11)
    - Television stations, undated, sleeve #29 (Box 11)
    - Temple Diesel, 1980 June 20, sleeve # 45 (Box 11)
    - Temple Instant Printing, undated, sleeve # 17 (Box 11)
    - Temple National Bank, 1978 June 28, sleeve # 11 (Box 11)
    - Temple Suzuki, 1970s, sleeve # 49 (Box 11)
    - Texaco, 1978 June 14, sleeve # 12 (Box 11)
    - Texas Bank, 1980 Aug. 22, sleeve # 48b (Box 11)
    - Thomas Hardware Store
      - 1980 Aug. 22, sleeve # 48b (Box 11)
      - Undated, sleeve #19 (Box 11)
    - Tobacco products, undated, sleeve #21 (Box 11)
    - Tourism, undated, sleeves #23-25, 31 (Box 11)
    - Tourist attractions, undated, sleeves #14, 15 (Box 11)
    - Triple D Mall and stores ( Tack and Western, VETS pets supplies), 1980 Aug. 7, sleeve # 43 (Box 11)
    - Triple D Tack and Western, 1980 Nov. 14, sleeve # 44 (Box 11)
    - Truck services, undated, sleeves #14, 26, 33 (Box 11)
    - United Furniture Sales, undated, sleeve # 46 (Box 11)
    - University Savings
      - 1980 June 20, sleeve # 45 (Box 11)
      - 1980 Nov. 14, sleeve # 44 (Box 11)
      - Undated, sleeve #18 (Box 11)
    - Video Central, undated, sleeve # 54 (Box 11)
    - Western Wear, undated, sleeve # 20 (Box 11)
    - Wheel's Restaurant, 1980 June 20, sleeve # 45 (Box 11)
    - Whittington's Beef Jerky, 1980 June 20, sleeve # 45 (Box 11)
    - Wildlife World
      - 1978 June 28, sleeve # 11 (Box 11)
      - 1979 Mar. 23, sleeve # 51 (Box 11)
    - Windmill Package and Barbecue Bar, 1980 Nov. 14, sleeve # 44 (Box 11)
    - Windmill Smokehouse, 1978 July 14, sleeve # 12 (Box 11)
  - Negatives from binder, undated (Box 12)
    - 1st Baptist Church, page 63 (Box 12)
    - 2 Mystery billboards, page 125 (Box 12)
    - 3 R Meat Shoppe, pages 44, 57, 58 (Box 12)
    - 39 Cent Hamburger, page 74 (Box 12)
    - 40th Anniversary, page 18 (Box 12)
    - 7-11, pages 17, 31, 32, 35, 38, 55, 56, 59, 63, 70, 71, 73, 74, 76, 77, 96, 97, 115, 120, 144 (Box 12)
    - 96.5, page 125 (Box 12)
    - A. Jackson, page 102 (Box 12)
    - A.J. Zubrek, page 68, 69, 78, 82 (Box 12)
    - Action Pawn, page 133 (Box 12)
    - Action World, page 32, 64, 81, 121, 143, 145, 148 (Box 12)
    - Adopt-a-Pet, page 76 (Box 12)
    - Alcoa, pages 114, 140 (Box 12)
    - Alcohol Consumption, pages 113, 115 (Box 12)
    - American's Diamond, page 125 (Box 12)
    - Amos, pages 58, 72 (Box 12)
    - Amos Electric, pages 32, 38 (Box 12)
    - Amtrak, page 16 (Box 12)
    - Anco Insurance, pages 80, 95 (Box 12)
    - Anniversary, page 8 (Box 12)
    - Antique Things, page 4 (Box 12)
    - Antiques (Texas Sampler), page 141 (Box 12)
    - Apple Creek, pages 103, 106, 108 (Box 12)
    - Aqualand, pages 51-53 (Box 12)
    - Aquarena Springs, pages 71, 73, 75, 78, 142 (Box 12)
    - Arby's, pages 69, 105 (Box 12)
    - Arkansas, page 108 (Box 12)
    - Audio Tech, pages 57, 58, 67 (Box 12)
    - August Moon, page 5 (Box 12)
    - Auto Body Clinic, pages 58, 79 (Box 12)
    - Auto Shack, page 141 (Box 12)
    - Auto Supply, page 121 (Box 12)
    - Autumn Chase, pages 91, 111 (Box 12)
    - B&C Bug Busters, pages 65, 86 (Box 12)
    - BH Settlement, page 120 (Box 12)
    - B's Pest Control, page 123 (Box 12)
    - B-93, page 125 (Box 12)
    - Barton Creek Square, page 125 (Box 12)
    - Bates Nissan, page 135 (Box 12)
    - Beal's Camera, page 109 (Box 12)
    - Beautify Temple, page 116 (Box 12)
    - Beech-Nut Tobacco, page 98 (Box 12)
    - Bell Air Conditioning, page 96 (Box 12)
    - Bell County Expo, pages 124, 126, 131 (Box 12)
    - Bell Crest, page 81 (Box 12)
    - Belton, pages 44, 136 (Box 12)
    - Belton Café, page 104 (Box 12)
    - Belton Repair, page 130 (Box 12)
    - Belton Rodeo, page 36 (Box 12)
    - Belton Teachers, pages 68, 119 (Box 12)
    - Ben's Western, page 51 (Box 12)
    - Benchmark, page 15a (Box 12)
    - Benchmark Inn, pages 41, 61, 86 (Box 12)
    - Benjamin's, pages 120, 133, 143, 144 (Box 12)
    - Bentley House, page 19 (Box 12)
    - Best Western, pages 39, 99, 109 (Box 12)
    - Beverly's, page 60 (Box 12)
    - Big 3 Auto, pages 78, 82 (Box 12)
    - Big Country Tree, page 102 (Box 12)
    - Big Gulp, pages 30, 38 (Box 12)
    - Big Top Amusements, page 51 (Box 12)
    - Bill Jones, page 83 (Box 12)
    - Blair and Potts, page 123 (Box 12)
    - Blank, page 6 (Box 12)
    - Blue Crest, page 96 (Box 12)
    - Boat Show, pages 53, 83 (Box 12)
    - Bob, page 1 (Box 12)
    - Bobby's, page 75 (Box 12)
    - Bobby's Burgers, page 86 (Box 12)
    - Bodee's Emporium, pages 124, 128 (Box 12)
    - Bonham PTO, page 127 (Box 12)
    - Booze Box, pages 11, 14 (Box 12)
    - Boy Scouts, page 144 (Box 12)
    - Brookshire Brothers, page 118 (Box 12)
    - Bruce and Ann's, page 93 (Box 12)
    - Bud, pages 5, 41, 86, 104, 109, 113 (Box 12)
    - Bud Light, pages 4, 39, 63, 83, 88, 91, 120, 122, 134, 139, 141, 142, 145, 147 (Box 12)
    - Budweiser, pages 6, 48, 50, 59, 62, 70, 72, 73, 89, 102, 117, 120, 130, 136, 138, 140-142 (Box 12)
    - Buffalo Bill's, page 97 (Box 12)
    - Burger Country, page 127 (Box 12)
    - Burger King, page 104 (Box 12)
    - Busch, page 17 (Box 12)
    - Butter Krust, page 50 (Box 12)
    - Buttercrust, page 8 (Box 12)
    - C. Bud Stockton, pages 54, 55, 79 (Box 12)
    - Cablevision, pages 109, 115, 119, 120, 127, 146 (Box 12)
    - CAC, pages 48, 64, 65, 67, 69, 75 (Box 12)
    - Cake, page 19 (Box 12)
    - Caldwell Bankers, page 18 (Box 12)
    - Camaro, page 73 (Box 12)
    - Cameron Ford, pages 65, 95, 106 (Box 12)
    - Canyon Creek, pages 61, 65 (Box 12)
    - Capri Cigarettes, pages 128, 147, 149 (Box 12)
    - Capture, page 142 (Box 12)
    - Car for Johnson Brother's Ford, page 43 (Box 12)
    - Carl's Jr., page 89 (Box 12)
    - Carpet Cleaners, pages 16, 121, 122, 147 (Box 12)
    - Catfish King, pages 121, 134, 135, 145 (Box 12)
    - Cattlemen's Round-Up, page 71 (Box 12)
    - Caught, page 119 (Box 12)
    - Cavender's Boot City, pages 134, 135, 137, 140, 148 (Box 12)
    - C-C Rodeo, page 33 (Box 12)
    - Celebrating Texas, pages 57, 58, 66 (Box 12)
    - Centel, pages 136, 144, 145 (Box 12)
    - Center of the Universe, page 89 (Box 12)
    - Center Universe, page 2 (Box 12)
    - Central Texas Bank, page 140 (Box 12)
    - Central Texas Boat Show, page 9 (Box 12)
    - Central Texas Counseling and Family Therapy Center, pages 117, 121, 127, 148 (Box 12)
    - Central Texas Orchestral Society, page 128 (Box 12)
    - Centroplex Home Products Show, page 15 (Box 12)
    - Century 21, pages 70, 77, 88, 97 (Box 12)
    - Certified Savings, page 60 (Box 12)
    - Chamber of Commerce, page 116 (Box 12)
    - Chapman Square, pages 91, 97, 101 (Box 12)
    - Chappell Hill, page 99 (Box 12)
    - Chappell Hill Apartments, page 148 (Box 12)
    - Chevrolet, pages 65, 77 (Box 12)
    - Children's Miracle Network Telethon, page 149 (Box 12)
    - Children's Rehab Telethon 1988, page 128 (Box 12)
    - Chiropractic Clinic, page 133 (Box 12)
    - Choice Rental, page 110 (Box 12)
    - Chrysler, page 119 (Box 12)
    - Church of Christ, page 65 (Box 12)
    - Cinema 6, page 145 (Box 12)
    - Circle J, page 61 (Box 12)
    - Citizen's Bank, page 98 (Box 12)
    - Citizen's National, page 99 (Box 12)
    - Citizen's State Bank, page 120 (Box 12)
    - Class of 1989, pages 113, 114, 136 (Box 12)
    - Classic Oldsmobile, pages 89, 108, 110, 112, 119, 120 (Box 12)
    - Cliff Jones, page 136 (Box 12)
    - CNB-Taylor, page 73 (Box 12)
    - Cochran, page 123 (Box 12)
    - Cochran Blair and Potts, page 117 (Box 12)
    - Coke, pages 5, 12, 14, 29 (Box 12)
    - Condos, pages 7, 9 (Box 12)
    - Construction (of billboards), pages 21-29, 31 (Box 12)
    - Coors, pages 81, 137, 139, 145 (Box 12)
    - Copy World, page 148 (Box 12)
    - Credit Union, page 22 (Box 12)
    - Crim Furniture, pages 95, 113, 114, 131 (Box 12)
    - Crimestoppers, pages 33, 34, 108 (Box 12)
    - Curry Office, pages 94, 96, 105 (Box 12)
    - Dairy Queen, pages 82, 140, 143 (Box 12)
    - Dakota, pages 85, 90 (Box 12)
    - Dan Kubiak, page 50 (Box 12)
    - David Collision, page 89 (Box 12)
    - Delta, page 49 (Box 12)
    - Designer Show, page 22 (Box 12)
    - DeWitt, pages 34, 60 (Box 12)
    - Diet Coke, pages 5-7 (Box 12)
    - Doc's 1 Stop, pages 61, 64, 65, 136, 137, 143 (Box 12)
    - Don Mabray, page 22 (Box 12)
    - Don Ringler Auto, pages 4, 12, 18, 30, 81 (Box 12)
    - Donna Williams 40th Birthday, page 124 (Box 12)
    - Dottie's Diner, page 60 (Box 12)
    - Doyle Phillips, pages 99, 102, 116, 119 (Box 12)
    - Doyle Phillips Steakhouse, page 118 (Box 12)
    - Doyle's Auto Supply, pages 117, 121, 126, 140 (Box 12)
    - Draeger Motor Co., pages 72, 74, 85, 95, 110 (Box 12)
    - Drew's Custom Homes, pages 45, 46 (Box 12)
    - Duck Criss, page 49 (Box 12)
    - Ducks Unlimited, page 135 (Box 12)
    - Duplex, pages 19, 58, 79, 93 (Box 12)
    - Ed Johnson's, pages 70, 74 (Box 12)
    - Edward D. Jones, pages 98, 100-102, 149 (Box 12)
    - Edward Jones, page 148 (Box 12)
    - Elaine's, page 60 (Box 12)
    - Elect Paul Reagan, pages 127, 146 (Box 12)
    - Emmanuel Baptist Church, pages 128, 129, 131 (Box 12)
    - Emporium, page 148 (Box 12)
    - Evco Supply, page 147 (Box 12)
    - Exxon, pages 57, 143 (Box 12)
    - E-Z Care, page 140 (Box 12)
    - Falcon Travel, pages 132, 134 (Box 12)
    - Family Reunion, page 47 (Box 12)
    - Family Reunion Restaurant, page 71 (Box 12)
    - Faraway Places, page 56 (Box 12)
    - Farm Bureau, page 68 (Box 12)
    - Farmers State Bank, page 54 (Box 12)
    - First Baptist, page 130 (Box 12)
    - First Baptist Choir, page 136 (Box 12)
    - First Baptist Church, pages 15, 95 (Box 12)
    - First Christian, page 30 (Box 12)
    - First Federal Savings, pages 15, 49, 51, 134 (Box 12)
    - First Med, pages 95, 99, 106, 107, 111, 112, 116, 119, 123, 128, 129, 131, 144, 145 (Box 12)
    - First National, pages 1, 99, 100, 109, 110 (Box 12)
    - First National Bank, pages 2, 5, 51, 96, 128, 133, 148, 149 (Box 12)
    - First National Bank--Georgetown, page 41 (Box 12)
    - First National Bank of Temple, pages 126, 129 (Box 12)
    - First Republic Bank, pages 2, 94 (Box 12)
    - Fisher-Vincent Ford, pages 82, 106, 131 (Box 12)
    - Fleets Inn, page 40 (Box 12)
    - Flowers by Tommy, page 19 (Box 12)
    - Floyd Campbell, pages 61, 67 (Box 12)
    - FNB, pages 45, 72, 90, 142, 143 (Box 12)
    - Food Mart, pages 126, 148 (Box 12)
    - Fountain of Beauty, page 4 (Box 12)
    - Foyt's, pages 105, 118 (Box 12)
    - FSB, pages 3, 79 (Box 12)
    - Garden Park Homes, page 17 (Box 12)
    - Garlyn Shelton, pages 74, 137, 144 (Box 12)
    - Gatorade, page 52 (Box 12)
    - Gemcraft Homes, page 34 (Box 12)
    - Georgetown, page 135 (Box 12)
    - Georgetown Hospital, page 145 (Box 12)
    - Georgetown Main Street, page 117 (Box 12)
    - Georgetown Roofing, pages 18, 19 (Box 12)
    - Ginny's, page 125 (Box 12)
    - Giovanni's, page 55 (Box 12)
    - Girl Scouts, pages 52, 53 (Box 12)
    - God and Country, page 36 (Box 12)
    - Grady Bailey, pages 61, 67 (Box 12)
    - Grandy's, pages 115, 133 (Box 12)
    - Grant Jones, pages 106, 111 (Box 12)
    - Greater Temple-Belton Telephone Directory, pages 129, 132 (Box 12)
    - Green's Sausage House, page 93 (Box 12)
    - Green Go's Liquor, page 139 (Box 12)
    - Greensleaves, page 126 (Box 12)
    - Gringo's Liquor, page 146 (Box 12)
    - Grower's, page 57 (Box 12)
    - Gunthrie, page 119 (Box 12)
    - Guthrie, page 111 (Box 12)
    - H.A. Wilson, pages 84, 110, 112 (Box 12)
    - Handicapped Children, page 85 (Box 12)
    - Hardee's, pages 14, 63, 84-86, 88, 109, 112, 113, 114, 147, 149 (Box 12)
    - Harding Motors, page 58 (Box 12)
    - Harding UMHB, page 48 (Box 12)
    - Harper T., page 40 (Box 12)
    - Harper-Talasek Funeral Homes, pages 40-42 (Box 12)
    - Harrison Logan, pages 62, 87, 101, 107, 108 (Box 12)
    - Haunted House (Jaycees), page 127 (Box 12)
    - HBO, page 3 (Box 12)
    - Health Expo, pages 86, 112 (Box 12)
    - Heartfield, page 91 (Box 12)
    - Heartfield Funeral Home, pages 92, 141 (Box 12)
    - Highshine, page 10 (Box 12)
    - Hofbrau, page 56 (Box 12)
    - Holiday Inn, page 19 (Box 12)
    - Home Health Equipment, pages 72, 77, 79, 80, 94, 109 (Box 12)
    - Home Place, page 78 (Box 12)
    - Hornsby Murcherson Funeral Home, page 125 (Box 12)
    - Hostages, pages 36, 59 (Box 12)
    - Houston Live Stock Show, pages 83, 88 (Box 12)
    - Howecons, page 38 (Box 12)
    - Hugh D. Shine, pages 69, 77 (Box 12)
    - Ice Cream Churn, page 136 (Box 12)
    - In Memoriam of the Challenger, page 58 (Box 12)
    - Industries, page 13 (Box 12)
    - Inn on the Creek, pages 97, 98, 104 (Box 12)
    - InterFirst, pages 4, 74, 94 (Box 12)
    - International, page 57 (Box 12)
    - IRA, page 62 (Box 12)
    - Ira Young Auto, pages 121, 147, 149 (Box 12)
    - J&A Tri-Star, pages 135, 145 (Box 12)
    - J.C. Garcia, page 86 (Box 12)
    - J.J.'s, pages 113, 114 (Box 12)
    - Jack in the Box, page 123 (Box 12)
    - Jack Ogg, page 49 (Box 12)
    - Jackson Health Care, pages 122, 147, 149 (Box 12)
    - Jackson Medical, page 138 (Box 12)
    - J.C. Penny, pages 67-69 (Box 12)
    - Jiffy Lube, page 125 (Box 12)
    - Jim Brady, page 50 (Box 12)
    - Jim Howe Homes, page 36 (Box 12)
    - Jim's Dive Shop, pages 61, 65, 93 (Box 12)
    - Jow Wyatt, pages 54, 79 (Box 12)
    - John Cunningham, page 32 (Box 12)
    - John Deere Tractors, page 125 (Box 12)
    - John Messer, pages 69, 73 (Box 12)
    - Johnnie's Cleaners, page 135 (Box 12)
    - Johnson Brothers Ford, pages 2, 42, 79, 80, 93, 140, 142, 148 (Box 12)
    - Jones Home and Auto, pages 74, 76, 86 (Box 12)
    - Judge Chambers, pages 10, 36 (Box 12)
    - Just Say Yes, page 122 (Box 12)
    - Ka-Tee Shoes, pages 44, 109 (Box 12)
    - KASE 101, page 15a (Box 12)
    - Kawasaki, page 67 (Box 12)
    - K-Bob's, pages 101, 104, 116, 133, 139, 140, 141 (Box 12)
    - KCEN-TV, pages 84, 102, 106, 112, 131, 134, 139, 145 (Box 12)
    - Kentucky Fried Chicken, page 140 (Box 12)
    - KIIZ, page 50 (Box 12)
    - Killeen, pages 21, 53 (Box 12)
    - Killeen Hilton, page 70 (Box 12)
    - King's Daughters, page 135 (Box 12)
    - King's Fried Chicken, page 53 (Box 12)
    - KIXS, page 52 (Box 12)
    - KLEN-TV, page 65 (Box 12)
    - Knight's Electronic Services, page 124 (Box 12)
    - Know When to Say When, page 74 (Box 12)
    - KOOV, pages 70, 75, 78, 91, 100, 111, 115, 118, 135, 139, 141 (Box 12)
    - KPLE, pages 13, 15a, 65 (Box 12)
    - KTEM, pages 13, 15a, 70, 88 (Box 12)
    - KTON, pages 36, 38 (Box 12)
    - Kuykendall, page 105 (Box 12)
    - KXXV, pages 46-48, 60, 64, 65, 70, 72, 74, 75, 100, 103, 105, 107, 109, 112 (Box 12)
    - La Quinta Inn, pages 101, 138 (Box 12)
    - Lakeside Clean-Up, pages 122, 131 (Box 12)
    - Lakeway Homes, page 15a (Box 12)
    - Lamar Student Council and Temple Police, page 148 (Box 12)
    - Lamplighter's, page 115 (Box 12)
    - Land, page 11 (Box 12)
    - Las Casas, pages 55, 75, 83, 103, 104, 115 (Box 12)
    - Lastovica, pages 91, 122, 126, 138 (Box 12)
    - Leasetown, page 68 (Box 12)
    - Lennox, page 119 (Box 12)
    - Leprechaun's Landing, pages 84, 92 (Box 12)
    - Lewis Chiropractic, page 139 (Box 12)
    - Like, page 5 (Box 12)
    - Lion's Eye Bank, page 52 (Box 12)
    - Lite Beer, page 125 (Box 12)
    - Little River Switch, pages 55, 56 (Box 12)
    - Little River Switch Steakhouse, page 53 (Box 12)
    - Little Valley Auto Ranch, page 61, 67 (Box 12)
    - Loading Chute, page 29 (Box 12)
    - Location shots, pages 2, 30, 70-72, 77 (Box 12)
    - Lock's Furniture Center, page 141 (Box 12)
    - Logan's Printing, pages 78, 79 (Box 12)
    - Lone Star Beer, page 85, 87, 89, 90, 105, 113, 114, 124, 130, 135, 136, 139, 145, 146, 148 (Box 12)
    - Long John Silver, pages 10, 86 (Box 12)
    - Longhorn Caverns, pages 6, 94 (Box 12)
    - Los Hermanos Mexican Restaurant, page 135, 141 (Box 12)
    - Lucenay Hearing Aids, pages 132, 133, 136 (Box 12)
    - Lynn Leigh Square, page 125 (Box 12)
    - Magic 105, page 95 (Box 12)
    - Main Street Video, pages 128, 129 (Box 12)
    - Mall, page 4 (Box 12)
    - March of Dimes, page 51 (Box 12)
    - Marlboro, pages 9, 10, 14, 16, 21, 31, 38, 44, 45, 48, 61, 64, 73, 75, 76, 97, 100, 101, 120, 138. 144, 145 (Box 12)
    - Martha's Vineyard, page 125 (Box 12)
    - Mary Hardin-Baylor University, page 116 (Box 12)
    - Maxwell Chrysler, page 69 (Box 12)
    - May Fest, pages 31, 65 (Box 12)
    - McLester and Grisham, page 34 (Box 12)
    - Meatball's, pages 103, 104 (Box 12)
    - Menthol Marlboro, page 117 (Box 12)
    - Merchant's Health Expo, page 88 (Box 12)
    - MHMR, pages 55, 56 (Box 12)
    - Midget Cafe, pages 61, 62 (Box 12)
    - Midway Junction, page 103 (Box 12)
    - Mike Kilpatrick, page 12 (Box 12)
    - Mikeska's BBQ, page 84 (Box 12)
    - Milan Chrysler, pages 114, 143 (Box 12)
    - Milan Dodge, pages 114, 140, 144 (Box 12)
    - Milan Dodge-Rockdale, pages 135, 147 (Box 12)
    - Mill Creek, pages 8, 11, 57 (Box 12)
    - Miller Beer, pages 2, 7, 125 (Box 12)
    - Mobil, pages 69, 101 (Box 12)
    - Mobil Chemical, page 127 (Box 12)
    - Mobile Home Park, page 54 (Box 12)
    - Mockingbird Chem-Dry, pages 118, 143 (Box 12)
    - Monarch Homes, pages 17, 34, 43, 97, 127 (Box 12)
    - Moons Balloons, page 12 (Box 12)
    - Moss & Moss, page 114 (Box 12)
    - Mr. Gatti's, pages 15a, 33, 133 (Box 12)
    - Mrs. Robinson's Neighborhood, pages 40, 69, 118, 130 (Box 12)
    - Murphey's, page 114 (Box 12)
    - National Telephone Exchange, pages 31, 37, 40, 41 (Box 12)
    - Natural Bridge Caverns, page 121 (Box 12)
    - Navy, page 147 (Box 12)
    - New Life Clinic, page 142 (Box 12)
    - Newswatch, pages 19, 33 (Box 12)
    - Norrell, page 84 (Box 12)
    - NPC, page 15 (Box 12)
    - Oak Bluff Estates, pages 139, 145 (Box 12)
    - Oak Creek, page 135 (Box 12)
    - Oak Ridge Corral, pages 119, 130, 133 (Box 12)
    - Oaks, page 123 (Box 12)
    - Oaks of Cedar Ridge, page 123 (Box 12)
    - Oatmeal, page 3 (Box 12)
    - Old Milwaukee, pages 138, 139 (Box 12)
    - Old Town Square, page 105 (Box 12)